<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="main_topic_names">
        <item>General Engineering and Applied Science</item>
        <item>Engineering Mathematics</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="geas_topic_names">
        <item>Physics</item>
        <item>Engineering Mechanics Statics</item>
        <item>Engineering Mechanics Dynamics</item>
        <item>Engineering Economy I</item>
        <item>Engineering Economy II</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="engg_math_topic_names">
        <item>Systems of Numbers &amp; Conversion</item>
        <item>Fundamentals in Algebra</item>
        <item>Quadratic Equation, Binomial Theorem &amp; Logarithms</item>
        <item>Age, Work, Mixture, Digit, Motion Problems</item>
        <item>Clock, Variation, Misc. Problems &amp; Progression</item>
        <item>Venn Diagram, Permutation, Combination &amp; Probability</item>
        <item>Plane Geometry</item>
        <item>Solid Geometry</item>
        <item>Plane Trigonometry</item>
        <item>Spherical Trigonometry</item>
        <item>Analytic Geometry I</item>
        <item>Analytic Geometry II</item>
        <item>Differential Calculus I</item>
        <item>Differential Calculus II</item>
        <item>Integral Calculus</item>
        <item>Differential Equations</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="main_topic_desc">
        <item>A discipline of science that applies existing scientific knowledge to develop more practical applications, like technology or inventions.</item>
        <item>The art of applying mathematics to complex real-world problems. It combines mathematical theory, practical engineering and scientific computing to address today’s technological challenges.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="geas_topic_desc">
        <item>natural science that involves the study of matter and its motion and behavior through space and time, along with related concepts such as energy and force.</item>
        <item>Graphical condition, Directional condition, Analytical condition, Friction, Parabolic Cable &amp; Catenary, Mass Moment of Inertia</item>
        <item>Rectilinear translation, Curvilinear translation, D'Alembert's Principle, Centifugal force</item>
        <item>Basic Terms, Market Situations, Simple Interest, Compound Interest, Nominal and Effective Rates of Interest, Discount</item>
        <item>Annuity, Depreciation, Bonds, Breakeven Analysis</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="engg_math_topic_desc">
        <item>System of Numbers and how to convert unit of measurement.</item>
        <item>Basic rules of Algebra, Properties of Equality, Zero, Exponents, Radicals, and Proportion, Special Products, and the Remainder &amp; Factor Theorem.</item>
        <item>Quadratic Equation, Binomial Theorem, Logarithms and It's properties.</item>
        <item>Solve problems about age, work, mixture, digit and motion.</item>
        <item>Solve about clock, variation, and other problems. learn about progressions</item>
        <item>Learn how to use venn diagram, Counting possible outcomes using permutation, combination, and learn what is probability theory.</item>
        <item>What is geometry, angles, circles, polygons, triangles, quadrilaterals, parallelograms and how to solve them.</item>
        <item>Learn about Polyhedrons, its properties, and how to get its surface area and volume for every kind of it.</item>
        <item>Study about triangles and it's properties.</item>
        <item>Solving triangular surfaces in a sphere and its applications.</item>
        <item>What is rectangular coordinates system, formulas for points, lines, and circle.</item>
        <item>Parabola, Ellipse, Hyperbola, and its properties.</item>
        <item>Limits, Definition of the Derivative, Derivatives of common functions</item>
        <item>Maxima, Minima &amp; Time Rates</item>
        <item>Indefinite integrals, Indefinite integrals of common functions, Definite integral</item>
        <item>a mathematical equation that relates some function with its derivatives</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>